Contact

srivallikadali9@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/srivalli-k-aa0b557a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

HAZOP Study

Hazard Analysis

hira

Certifications

OH&S Management systems auditor/Lead auditor training course (BS OHSAS 18001:2007)

Environmental Management system training course (ISO 14001:2015)

Srivalli k

Health Safety Environment Coordinator at Superior Energy Services

Dehradun

Summary

Experienced Health and Safety Cultural Assessments, Hazard Identification & Risk Assessments, Failure Mode and Effects Analysis (FMEA), Fault Tree Analysis (FTA) or Event Tree Analysis (ETA),

Developing HSE Management System by using Strategic Planning including safety audits and In-house training programs, Behavior-Based Safety (BBS) management, implementation of DMRC Safety Manual, Safety policy of the company, and other safety management systems like BOCW act 1996 & OHSAS/ISO

Experience

Superior Energy Services
Health Safety Environment Coordinator
March 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months)
Nagayalanka

CLOVERS SAFETY SERVICES PRIVATE LIMITED HSE Coordinator July 2017 - June 2018 (1 year)

- Develop and maintain HSE Management System for clients by using Strategic Planning including safety audits and In-house training programs, Behavior-Based Safety (BBS) management
- Conduct Health and Safety Cultural Assessments by using either Hazard Identification & Risk Assessments, Failure Mode and Effects Analysis (FMEA), Fault Tree Analysis (FTA) or Event Tree Analysis (ETA)
- Maintain and update training manuals, Safety Management Systems and reports

J.Kumar CRTG (JV)
HSE trainee
January 2017 - May 2017 (5 months)
Delhi

- Conduct Tool Box Talk, regular Safety Walks to observe Excavation, sheet pile support with hammer, crane operations, hot & cold works, works on scaffolding & work at height in the construction area of Metro project
- Ensure implementation of DMRC Safety Manual, Safety policy of the company, and other safety management systems like BOCW act 1996 & OHSAS/ISO
- · Compliance to maintain statutory and legal requirements
- Monitor and prevent unsafe acts and conditions by eliminating unsafe equipment and tools and improving Behavior-Based Safety

Education

University of Petroleum and Energy Studies Master of Technology (M.Tech.), Health safety and environment · (2015 - 2017)

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Kakinada Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Petrochemical engineering · (2010 - 2014)

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Kakinada B.Tech, Petrochemical Engineering (2010 - 2014)

Andhra Pradesh Board of Intermediate Education Srichaitanya College

XII, Maths Physics and chemistry (2008 - 2010)

Andhra Pradesh Board of Secondary EducationMaharshi High School

X, SSC · (2007 - 2008)